export const data = [
    {
        question : 'A particle starts from rest and moves with a uniform acceleration of "2m/s\u00B2". What is its velocity after 10 seconds?',
        option1 : '10 m/s',
        option2 : '20 m/s',
        option3 : '40 m/s',
        option4 : '50 m/s',
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : 'A spring with a spring constant ùëò=200N/m is stretched by 0.1 m. What is the potential energy stored in the spring?',
        option1 : '1 J',
        option2 : '2 J',
        option3 : '0.5 J',
        option4 : '00.5 J',
        ans : 1,
    },
    {
        question : 'Which of the following has the highest bond angle?',
        option1 : 'NH\u2083',
        option2 : 'H\u20820',
        option3 : 'CH\u2084',
        option4 : 'CO\u2082',
        ans : 4,
    },
    {
        question : 'Which gas is most soluble in water?',
        option1 : 'O\u2082',
        option2 : 'H\u2082',
        option3 : 'NH\u2083',
        option4 : 'CH\u2084',
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : 'The sum of the first 20 terms of the arithmetic progression: 2, 4, 6, 8, ... is:',
        option1 : '420',
        option2 : '440',
        option3 : '400',
        option4 : '460',
        ans : 2,
    },
    {
        question : 'A ball is thrown vertically upwards with a velocity of 20m/s. How long will it take to reach its maximum height?',
        option1 : '1s',
        option2 : '2s',
        option3 : '3s',
        option4 : '4s',
        ans : 2,
    },
    {
        question : 'Two resistors of 6Œ© and 12Œ© are connected in parallel. What is their equivalent resistance?',
        option1 : '4Œ©',
        option2 : '5Œ©',
        option3 : '3Œ©',
        option4 : '8Œ©',
        ans : 1,
    },
    {
        question : 'The pH of a 0.001 M HCl solution is:',
        option1 : '1',
        option2 : '2',
        option3 : '3',
        option4 : '4',
        ans : 3,
    },
    {
        question : 'The time period of a simple pendulum is 2s. What will be its length?',
        option1 : '1 m',
        option2 : '2 m',
        option3 : '0.5 m',
        option4 : '0.25 m',
        ans : 1,
    },
    {
        question : 'What is the pH of a 0.01 M NaOH solution?',
        option1 : '10',
        option2 : '12',
        option3 : '2',
        option4 : '11',
        ans : 2,
    },
    {
        question : 'Exam Kisa likha Vaheed Bhai',
        option1 : 'Bad',
        option2 : 'Good',
        option3 : 'Maharshi',
        option4 : 'Very Good',
        ans : 2,
    }
]